[{"answer": "You said it, when you said the C word.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "What is it about the particular chemistry of you five now you think that's been so you successful?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "And I really would like to change the word fear and just replace with it a healthy concern.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Is actually likely that this is going to happen now from all that you see?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "I think there's a lot of rain.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What do you think about the possibility of a direct hit on Haiti or even just very extensive rain damage?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "I mean, the economy is issue number one, two, three, four and five in this election, even though these other issues have come and been part of the dialogue every day.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Are we going to see issues like abortion come into the fore or is it going to be swept away by the economy?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well, and probably even more than that is that he's not look like us.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Do you think that's fair?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "I think that what's more important is that we bring the candidates on, we bring both parties on, and we let the audience make that decision for them.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Or do you think it's an easy bit of rhetoric that actually what you're looking at is historical positions of the Republican Party that are just slowly going slightly out of fashion?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I believe it's the economy.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "What is your gut feeling about what real Americans care about?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "I think we have to be able to offer the widest range of story and sample that we can.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Tell me when you get, you know, a run of things like the convention now then the election, what do you think collectively you guys need to bring as a show to the American audience?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "After you've gone through breast cancer as I did in 2007, and unfortunately, this is because of some of the treatment, saved my life.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "But are you scared in yourself?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Unbelievable.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "And she's is a remarkable woman, isn't she, the way that she's been dealing with this?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "It was pretty amazing because -- like you said, it's something that hadn't happened in so many years.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "I mean, George, for you, guys, does it get better than that, the morning TV battle?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "I want to make it better.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "What do you want to do with the show?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "I think it's what we touched on all show.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Let me ask you, Lara, what do you feel collectively has made the difference here between you and \"The Today Show\" this year?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I love that you picked on me for this.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Do you all hate each other behind closed doors?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "We don't take joy in what's happening in other places.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "So once you got a chance to sample it, how could you not choose that show?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "It was great to be able to talk about him in so fitting -- in so fitting a way and before so many people that -- for whom he would be happy that I was in front of and for the reason I was.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "When you made that speech, what was going through your mind?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "In bed.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "In bed?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "I'm reading the history of Islam.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "What do you read?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Of course I do.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Do you read \"In Style\" magazine in bed, George?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "I can just pick up the ruins.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "That might be the question that I've heard the most, Piers.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What on Earth are you thinking?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "The Rocket is almost firing on all cylinders.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Is the Rocket firing on all cylinders?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Yes, everybody is saying that.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "This is what the real game plan is, isn't it, Roger?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well, a great question.", "docId": "120823pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "I want to come back out and show people what I'm still made of?", "qSentId": 616}]